Liel Amar

E-mailliel@lielamar.comDate of birthMarch 18th, 2001Websitelielamar.comMobile+972 (54) 974-1803GitHubgithub.com/LielAmarAddressGilo, Jerusalem

Expert developer with 5+ years of experience in a variety of languages, technologies, large-scale systems, applications, and games. A natural leader with proven capabilities in team management, public assistance, employee nurturing and tutoring, creating and executing work plans. Creative, inquisitive, and autodidact.

Professional Experience

March 2015 - Current

Bukkit Developer

- Developing Minestore, an integration system between Minecraft and NodeJS Web applications that handles the selling of in-game perks and items, like Buycraft, but with in-game verification to solve chargeback issues.
- Developed my own set of libraries, including but not limited to Packets, Scoreboards, Bossbars, Validation, and Map Management.
- Developed large-scale minigames such as Party Games and ArmsRace, supporting multiple databases, full configuration, in-game control, and developer API.
- Developed LanguageFix, the biggest plugin to solve RTL issues in Minecraft.
- Developed utilities such as Two Factor Authentication and CompletePermissions.

April 2020 - Current

Cybernet's Attendance System | Cybernet, Israel

- Designing and implementing a Web application using NodeJS, Express, and MySQL.
- Testing, deploying, and maintaining the application.

August 2019 - April 2020

Developer, Unit Co-Founder & Leader | Israel Defense Forces, Israel

- Designed, implemented, tested, deployed, and maintained a secured real-time location-based Web application and Windows applications using various programming languages and tools.
- Provided units with evaluations, demonstrations, and samples.
- Recruited, trained, and managed soldiers, pushed their personal development.
- Collaborated with other brigades, shared resources, and knowledge.

July 2017 - July 2019

Team Leader, Java Developer | Oversight, Israel

- Managed and maintained 20 Spigot servers on Linux and Windows machines.
- Designed and developed 7 large-scale Minecraft minigames.
- Led weekly development work meetings and monthly meetings with the volunteer team.

Volunteer Positions & Personal Projects

July 2019 - Current

Staff Member | Hypixel

- Providing in-game assistance to players and general moderation.
- Training and mentoring new staff members.
- Finding bugs, testing new updates, and minigames.

August 2016 - July 2017

Server Manager, Developer | Play-IL, Israel

- Recruited, trained, and guided new and old staff members.
- Developed new minigames, released updates, patched bugs, and exploits.
- Led weekly work meetings and monthly community events.

August 2014 - Current

Developer

- Developing a discord bot capable of self-moderation, automated minigames, private channels, and support systems using Python 3.
- Developed Android applications such as MyCinema, an advanced movie list, and WaiTime, a virtual map of places with a heavy load of customers.

Video Editor, Designer

- Editing High-Quality videos and creating 3D Minecraft animations.
- Designing logos, banners, and pictures.

Education and Languages

2019 - Graduated with emphasis on Computer Science from "Ort's College" High-School, Jerusalem.

2020 - Design Patterns in Java Course

Hebrew - Native language

English - Fluent speaker